[{"answer": "I think he's going to announce a number of projects, a number of things that will put America back to work.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Do you think President Obama is going to announce anything on Thursday which will get America back to work?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't had any involvement in the speech, itself.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "You seem to be very well-informed on what the president may be saying?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "I mean, look at the background.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Do you think that he has it in him to come up with a plan which is going to be big enough, radical enough and effective enough to really transform this jobs crisis?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, in many ways they don't play by the rules.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Did you agree with that?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "They have a significant responsibility that they haven't been taking up.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "So where does employer, American employer, responsibility kick in here?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "We do need the revenue.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Everyone over $1 million a year, I'm going to tax the hell out of you, because we need revenue, we need this economy back on its feet?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "We want our president to succeed.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Congressman, you're not very impressed then by what you think may be coming?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, I would hope that the president would call on the government's capacity to be able to spend money into circulation, just like the Fed, to create money out of nothing to quantitative easing.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "What kind of thing has President Obama got to come out with to really make a difference here?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "UCINICH: Well, your conventional political analysis is spot-on.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "So, where is the incentives of the Republicans to not play partisan games here?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Because -- is it going to be a shoo-in for the president do you think when it comes to it, because no one is quite sure what the GOP stand for?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not a candidate.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Could you see a situation where you or somebody else thinks he knows something we need to have a different face here?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, there is something to what Kipling wrote about if you can keep your head while those about you are losing theirs and blaming it on you, there is something to that.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Why doesn't he say, you know something, I'm the president of the United States to John Boehner and if you want to move your thing, you move it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Hinge on the speech, no.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Without being too dramatic about it, I mean, could the prospect of a second term of office for Barack Obama hinge on this speech on Thursday?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "It would be very difficult.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "I mean, slightly rephrasing then, my previous point -- if those jobs are not created, and in fact, if there is continued unemployment and the figure goes up, it is going to be almost impossible, isn't it, for President Obama to win the election?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Is it time for a bit of audacity and hope?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Well, we're certainly seeing them spin out of control in terms of command and control.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "The obvious question is -- post the killing of Osama bin Laden and other al Qaeda leaders being bumped off, too, are we seeing the end of al Qaeda as an effective terrorist organization?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I was fairly certain from the time I met bin Laden -- and this is not revisionist history.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you had that extraordinary encounter that he might be capable of pulling off such an atrocity?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Well, I think two opposing forces have met there.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "And it would be almost impossible for a terrorist group now to carry out something that nobody had thought of?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Well, it is both.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Or is it both?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, al Zawahiri is an interesting man.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What will be going through his mind now, as he tries to regroup and rally his troops, do you think?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it is no secret to any of us that a lot of television production involves bluff.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "But does that kind of sum up really the fact that al Qaeda has managed to bluff the world into thinking that its this incredibly sophisticated, glamorous outfit, when actually it looks like they are just like another bunch of terrorists who may have got lucky a few times?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, the analysis division in the DNI is the overarching group that has the group of people who prepare the PDA, or the Presidents' Daily Briefing.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "You guys have to be lucky every minute of every day?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Well, al Qaeda is the key threat to killing Americans on U.S. soil or overseas in rapid operations.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Or from everything that you have picked up over the last few years, are there other organizations that you think may -- or even lone individuals that pose a bigger threat?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, power abhors a vacuum.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Would you think that we need to be finding out pretty quickly who is going to be running these countries?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I'm an optimist by nature.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "What is your personal view, from all that you have seen?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I think America has been preparing incrementally for ten years since 9/11.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How does America prepare for this kind of event?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "ILLER: Well, I think, as you said a little further back in this show, you're always trying to out-imagine the bad guys.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What is the doomsday event as far as intelligence operatives go, when it comes to this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "I have to say, the DNI, the Director of National Intelligence, is by and large a policy shop that is meant to lead the intelligence community.", "docId": "110906pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Are you a slightly relieved that you no longer have to have this responsibility bearing down on your shoulders?", "qSentId": 448}]